http://www.bronxarts.org/privacy-policy/

HomeAboutMissionWho We AreOur BoardOur TeamFinancialsPressProgramsConnector ProgramsArtist ResidenciesSu-CasaBronx Memoir ProjectCommunity ProgramsLongwood Arts ProjectLongwood Art GalleryYouth Engagement ProgramResource Programs@2700Artist RegistryGrantsArtist Sustainability Workshop SeriesAdvocate ProgramsCultural Assets MapCultural History MapConvenings and PartnershipsGrantsNew WorkArts FundCommunity ArtsArts on the BlockBronx Recognizes its Own (BRIO)OpportunitiesCOVID-19 ResourcesCall For ArtistsJobs/InternshipsStudio SpaceResidencies/GrantsFellowships/ScholarshipsSubmit An OpportunityEventsSubmit An EventGet InvolvedLog InDonateMembershipBecome a Grants PanelistContact UsVolunteerDonate
My Cart 0
Home>Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Please read this Terms of Use and Privacy Agreement (“Agreement”) carefully before using Bronx Council on the Arts Website (“Website”). Your use of the Website is subject to your acceptance of this Agreement.
User Information and Privacy
We have created this Terms of Usage and Privacy Statement to help show Bronx Council on the Arts’ commitment to privacy. This Statement describes Bronx Council on the Arts’ information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site.
We do not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address unless you voluntarily submit it. If you send us personal correspondence, such as e-mails or letters, we may collect them into a file specific to you. If, at any time, you do not wish to receive e-mail from us, please send a message to info@bronxarts.org requesting that we stop.
We do use cookies to track non-personal information about our Website’s users such as the URL that the user has come from and goes to next, the Internet browser and type of operating system used, the user’s location, and the user’s IP address. We use IP addresses for system administration purposes so we can better understand which parts of our Web site users visit most. Many sites automatically collect this information. We may use this information for such purposes as improving the content of our Website, marketing, advertising or research.
We do reserve the right to release current or past user information internally within Bronx Council on the Arts and its affiliates, partners, and subsidiaries. We also reserve the right to release current or past user information to third parties for limited purposes if we believe that usage is (i) in violation of this Agreement; (ii) used to commit unlawful acts; and/or (iii) is required to be disclosed to comply with applicable laws or regulations or with a court or administrative order. Except as stated in this paragraph, we will not share information specific to users with third parties. We may, however, disclose aggregate user information to third parties.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.
We minimally use third party services that could potentially track your user data such as:
Embedded Google maps are used only where applicable
Social media sharing scripts are only invoked through outbound links when the user initiates sharing
No other third party hosted scripts are used
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Sharing
We share aggregated demographic information with our funders. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
Our Sponsors
Contact
2700 East Tremont Avenue, Bronx, NY 10461
(718) 931-9500
Follow Us
Mission
A pioneering advocate for cultural equity, the Bronx Council on the Arts nurtures the development of a diverse array of artists and arts organizations and builds strong cultural connections in and beyond The Bronx.
Support Us
Donate
BCA Newsletter Signup Form
Stay informed by subscribing.
Submit
Programs
Grants
Events
Copyright © 2020 Bronx Council On The Arts. All Rights Reserved.  |  					Privacy Policy  |
Terms & Conditions
Designed & Powered by Design Brooklyn
Log In
Forgot your password?
•
Don't have an account?
